(Sheldon:)I question your premise.
(Sheldon:)How is a new suit going to prevent me
from passing out...
(Sheldon:)...in front of a ballroom
full of people?
(Penny:)It'll give you confidence.
(Penny:)Sometimes when I'm feeling
stressed out...
(Penny:)...I go out and buy a cute top
or a fun skirt...
(Penny:)...and I have a whole new outlook
on life.
(Sheldon:)Don't you eventually realize
you're the same stressed-out person...
(Sheldon:)...in a cute top or a fun skirt?
(Penny:)Yeah, that's when I buy shoes.
Now, let's see what we got.
Oh. This is nice.
It's only one color.
Yes, so?
(Sheldon:)That's a lot of money
for only one color.
(Penny:)Fine. Why don't you pick out
what you like?
(Sheldon:)Hmm.
SHELDON:
This is pretty sharp.